<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adrià Céspedes</title><link>http://www.example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Adrià Céspedes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About me</title><link>http://www.example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about Agile methodologies, an expert in leading technology projects with more than a decade of experience working with Mobile and Web technologies.
Credentials PMP® certified and Master in Project Management by EAE Business School and UPC, Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Information Technology and Services, Information Technology and Services with a major in Management of Services from the “Escuelas Universitarias Gimbernat y Tomàs Cerdà” and the “Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona”.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://www.example.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.example.com/contact/</guid><description>You can reach me on LinkedIn</description></item><item><title>Work</title><link>http://www.example.com/work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.example.com/work/</guid><description>As Agile Project Manager at Coverfy, the Barcelona-based insurtech startup that allows users to manage all insurance and optimize prices and coverage from a mobile device, I am responsible for the definition and leadership of the different projects. I grew up a team of 6 developers working on Scrum methodology, improving the team performance by introducing Scrum with a Lean mindset and aligning team goals with business goals.
  As an IT Project Manager for Institut Municipal d&amp;rsquo;Informàtica (Ajuntament de Barcelona), I was responsible for developing new features for CRM DAC project that uses Microsoft Dynamics as an integrating tool for the data of all the citizens (3.</description></item></channel></rss>